ppgazette.com 2012-06-09

# Printable Grocery Coupons, free online coupons | PPGazette

PPGazette.com (Company) recognizes online privacy as a valid and important issue. The following Policy outlines what information we collect, how we go about collecting it, under what circumstances the information is shared with third parties, and your choices to determine what communications you receive from us and from our marketing partners. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT PROVIDE THE COMPANY WITH ANY INFORMATION OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON COMPANY WEB SITES. 

Company Customer Choices

Your California Privacy Rights 

Beginning January 1, 2005, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to either (1) a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or (2) be notified of a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. 

To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties, send your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to: 

Penny Pincher Gazette, PO Box 303393, Austin, TX 78703

How We Use The Information We Collect 

This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on the PPGazette.com website. We may use the personal information that you supply to us and work with third parties to bring retail opportunities to you via direct mail, email and telemarketing. These third parties may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including but not limited to lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression, validation and email marketing services. When you register with PPGazette.com and you leave the box checked stating “Yes, I want to receive information and offers from Bargain-PPGazette.com” – you explicitly authorize us to share your information with Datran Media to contact you via email. 

In order to participate in PPGazette.com, you must first submit the information requested. When submitting user information, you will have the option to subscribe to the PPGazette.com newsletter, a periodic email communicating various offers that we think you might like based on the registration information you provided and any offers that you selected in this promotion. You may unsubscribe from this newsletter, or any Company email, at any time by clicking on the automated link provided at the end of the email. Note that you may continue to receive email from persons or entities other than the Company. 

We request a limited amount of personal information from consumers who participate in the promotions on this site. This information includes, but is not limited to the following consumer Information: 

Your name, email address, mailing address, birth date, password

THE COMPANY MAY USE THE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANYS SOLE DISCRETION. PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT WE MAY TRANSFER YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS AND MARKETERS FOR VARIOUS MARKETING PURPOSES, INCLUDING THEIR ON-LINE AND/OR OFF-LINE PROGRAMS OR SERVICES. 

By subscribing to the PPGazette.com newsletter, you are consenting to receive commercial e-mail that informs you about new merchandise, sales, special discounts and promotions. If you no longer wish to receive email, follow the instructions at the bottom of every email. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We also may use the information that you provide for various non-marking purposes. 

We use information provided by users of this Web site to enhance their usage of this and similar Web sites. We create internal reports on user demographics and traffic patterns to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and promotions, and to report results to our marketing partners. We do not use any personally identifiable information to compile these reports. 

Company may disclose your information if it is required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to edicts of law or comply with legal processes; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Companys advertising service, or (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any user of the Companys advertising service. 

How We Collect Information 

We collect and use information as follows: 

Survey Information

We collect information from consumers by various methods, including but not limited to when a consumer completes a registration page. We also may collect information about you from other sources and use that information in combination with information provided from this Web site. 

Third Party Lists

The Company collects information regarding consumers when a consumer provides information to a third party and the Company subsequently purchases, licenses or otherwise acquires the information from the third party. When acquiring this information, the Company seeks assurances that the seller or provider of this information has the right to transfer this information to the Company and that the consumers whose personal information is included on the list opted-in to the list. 

Cookies 

A cookie is a small text file stored on a users computer for record-keeping purposes. The Company uses cookies to enable users to be routed properly through our site. We also provide links to external advertisers and marketing partner companies; these sites may choose to use cookies to better promote their products and services. 

Our advertisers and marketing partners have their own privacy procedures and policies that are not controlled by the Company. We encourage our users to be aware of the individual privacy policies of every Web site that the user contacts. 

Log Files

Log files are also used to track and monitor traffic patterns on our site. They are not used to track or monitor personally identifiable information. 

User Feedback/Inquiries 

Users may contact the Company with feedback, questions or comments or for assistance, either through the Companys customer service department or otherwise. The Company uses this information to respond to the feedback, questions or comments and to provide customer service. 

No Information Collected from Children

We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. We are committed to carefully protecting privacy where children are involved no matter the point of contact. In particular, our intention is to fully comply with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Per COPPA guidelines, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information through any point of contact, we ask to be contacted at Contact Us and we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files. 

Delete/Deactivate Policy 

A user may unsubscribe from our electronic mailings by following the instructions that we include at the end of every mailing. To correct, update or request that we delete information you provided, please email us at info@PPGazette.com, or write to us at: 

Penny Pincher Gazette, 9430 Research Blvd. Suite 200, Austin, TX 78759

Notification Of Changes To Privacy Policy 

>From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will revise this Policy accordingly. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

General Security Policy 

The Company attempts to meet and/or exceed standards of online privacy. When you submit information, your information is protected both on-line and off-line in accordance with applicable laws, regulations and industry standards. 

Last revised: June 10, 2008
